var questionArr = [
    {
        // questionNumber: "Math-1",
        question: "What is the name of Taylor Swift's first album?",
        firstOption: "Midnights",
        secondOption: "Lover",
        thirdOption: "Reputation",
        fourthOption: "Taylor Swift",
        correctAnswer: "#fourth-option"
    },
    {
        // questionNumber: "Math-2",
        question: "Which of the following songs of Taylor swift's is more popular than the other options?",
        firstOption: "Blank Space",
        secondOption: "Lavender Haze",
        thirdOption: "Cruel Summer",
        fourthOption: "End game",
        correctAnswer: "#first-option"
    },
    {
        // questionNumber: "Math-3",
        question: "Which song of taylor swift's did you first add to your playlist, 'T-Swift'? ",
        firstOption: "Wildest Dreams",
        secondOption: "We are never ever getting back together",
        thirdOption: "willow",
        fourthOption: "Lover",
        correctAnswer: "#second-option"
    },
    {
        // questionNumber: "Math-4",
        question: "What is the square of the number of Spotify followers you have?",
        firstOption: "225",
        secondOption: "169",
        thirdOption: "155",
        fourthOption: "144",
        correctAnswer: "#second-option"
    },
    {
        // questionNumber: "Math-5",
        question: "How many people do you follow on Spotify?",
        firstOption: "17",
        secondOption: "19",
        thirdOption: "12",
        fourthOption: "20",
        correctAnswer: "#second-option"
    },
  
    {
        // questionNumber: "English-1",
        question: "Who is the lead singer of the band sharing the name as the one your parents wanted to give you? ",
        firstOption: "Dave Grohl",
        secondOption: "Michael Jackson",
        thirdOption: "Adam Levine" ,
        fourthOption: "Kurt Cobain",
        correctAnswer: "#fourth-option"
    },
    {
        // questionNumber: "English-2",
        question: "In what song does Taylor sing: “She wears high heels, I wear sneakers…”?",
        firstOption: "Shake it off",
        secondOption: "You will never be alone",
        thirdOption: "You belong with me",
        fourthOption: "Cruel Summer",
        correctAnswer: "#third-option"
    },
    {
        // questionNumber: "English-3",
        question: "Which color have you most prominently wore in your highlight, 'fit check', be it a top or bottom",
        firstOption: "black",
        secondOption: "green",
        thirdOption: "orange",
        fourthOption: "blue",
        correctAnswer: "#first-option"
    },
    {
        // questionNumber: "English-4",
        question: "At which non-school location did you, Misha and Pragya hang out alone for the first time?",
        firstOption: "Your 2021 birthday bar",
        secondOption: "Pragya's House",
        thirdOption: "Mishas's House",
        fourthOption: "Dubai Mall",
        correctAnswer: "#third-option"
    },
   
    {
        // questionNumber: "History-1",
        question: "What is your position in the football team?",
        firstOption: "Left winger",
        secondOption: "Striker",
        thirdOption: "Right center back",
        fourthOption: "Attacking midfielder",
        correctAnswer: "#second-option"
    },
    {
        // questionNumber: "History-2",
        question: "What is your favorite song?",
        firstOption: "Hundred Miles",
        secondOption: "Woman",
        thirdOption: "Give me everything",
        fourthOption: "On the floor",
        correctAnswer: "#fourth-option"
    },
   
    {
        // questionNumber: "History-4",
        question: "Who is your bestie?",
        firstOption: "Pragya",
        secondOption: "Misha",
        thirdOption: "Anannya",
        fourthOption: "Yohaan",
        correctAnswer: "#fourth-option"
    },
   
  
    {
        // questionNumber: "Language-2",
        question: "What song do Anannya and Yohaan keep singing?",
        firstOption: "Closer",
        secondOption: "Don't let me down",
        thirdOption: "Colors",
        fourthOption: "Starboy",
        correctAnswer: "#first-option"
    },
    
  

]